

Lagos, Nigeria, +234 7067069561, chinedugabrie29@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a front-end developer focused on crafting clean & user-friendly experiences, I am passionate about building excellent software that improves the lives of those around me and I am ready to take on challenges using problem-solving and task prioritization skills to help the team succeed.

EXPERIENCE

IT Consultant

HR Consultant
APPWORLD Lagos, Nigeria

January 2022 - May 2022

- Brought in highly qualified applicants and targeted recruitment strategies in key candidate pools.
- Addressed employee relations issues, harassment allegations, and work complaints.
- Performed manual and automated tasks with detailed instructions from supervisors.

Nigerian Institute for Industrial Security I Lagos – Nigeria

January 2020 - February 2021

- Built automation into technical systems to help with repetitive tasks.
- Configured software solutions to meet customers' business process requirements.
- Employed consultative skills to assess user needs and develop and deliver technical training.
- Followed up and handled inbound leads with online web sales and marketing channels.
- Kept organization at forefront of technological advances, tracking new technologies and integrating best-fit options
- Improved system usability by consulting with end-users to identify deficiencies and missing features.

Web Designer January 201B - February 2019 APPWORLD I Lagos, Nigeria APPWORLD I Lagos, Nigeria

- Assessed complex technical designs for opportunities for simplification and user satisfaction improvements.
- Prepared website low-fidelity wireframes and high-fidelity mockups for developers and project managers.
- Updated design based on current web trends, technology changes, and style improvements.
- Improved usability and appearance of eCommerce booking and other site features.
- Developed design ideas in Adobe Photoshop for different stages of web design and development.
- Created highly responsive and scalable web applications for different clients.
- created an accessible web front-end user interface for new or existing clients with a combination technologies such as HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT and WordPress.

Computer Systems Administrator APPWORLD I Lagos, Nigeria

February 2017 - February 2019

- Supported users with training, technical assistance- and network improvements.
- Helped the technical team install, configure and customize company-wide systems.
- Corrected hardware. software and network connectivity issues by diagnosing faults and completing skilled repairs.
- Prevented data Loss with regular backups and sound disaster recovery processes.
- Monitor system performance according to industrial requirements.

SKILLS

- Proficient knowledge of HTML
- Proficient knowledge of CSS
- Proficient knowledge of JAVASCRIPT
- Proficient With WordPress
- Proficient With Figma
- Proficient With Affinity Photo and Affinity Designer
- Employee relations
- Policy development
- Retention management
- Recruitment and hiring
- Benefits administration
- Good communication
- Issue troubleshooting
- Team player

EDUCATION

BSC HONS Computer Science {Second Class Upper Division* - Computer Science ECOLE SUPERIESURE DE MANAGEMENT UNIVERSITE Benin Republic

November 2017